export const quizStructure = {
  "Overview Of A Computer System": [
    {
      unitName: "Computer Basics",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the name of an electronic tool that facilitates the input, processing, and output of information?",
          options: ["Operating system", "Motherboard", "Computer"],
          correctAnswer: "Computer",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the term for a small picture that represents a folder, program, or other items on a computer?",
          options: ["Desktop", "Icon", "Graphic"],
          correctAnswer: "Icon",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the part of a computer that allows a user to input information?",
          correctAnswer: "Input Device",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: The CPU is referred to as the brain of the computer, responsible for calculations, movement, and processing of information.",
          correctAnswer: "True",
          type: "true or false"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the name of the computer's short-term memory that is lost when the computer is turned off?",
          options: ["CPU", "Hardware", "RAM"],
          correctAnswer: "RAM",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the computer part that connects all other components, enabling them to communicate and work together?",
          options: ["Operating System", "Disk Drive", "Motherboard"],
          correctAnswer: "Motherboard",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What term is used to describe the physical components of a computer?",
          correctAnswer: "Hardware",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "What are the parts of a computer called that allow the user to see or hear information produced by the computer?",
          options: ["Software", "Input Device", "Output Device"],
          correctAnswer: "Output Device",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the computer part called that stores programs and information on two or more disks within the computer?",
          options: ["Motherboard", "Hard Drive", "CPU"],
          correctAnswer: "Hard Drive",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the name of the computer part that reads information from a disk?",
          options: ["Disk System", "Motherboard", "Disk Drive"],
          correctAnswer: "Disk Drive",
          type: "multiple choice"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      unitName: "Computer Operations",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "What is another term for computer programs?",
          correctAnswer: "Software",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the name of the program that controls a computer's basic functions?",
          options: ["Hard Drive", "Motherboard", "Operating System"],
          correctAnswer: "Operating System",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following numbers is a binary number?",
          options: ["1 and 2", "1 and 0.1", "0 and 1"],
          correctAnswer: "0 and 1",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which language does the computer understand?",
          options: ["Computer understands only C Language", "Computer understands only Assembly Language", "Computer understands only Binary Language"],
          correctAnswer: "Computer understands only Binary Language",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which computer language is written in binary codes only?",
          options: ["English", "Machine language", "C"],
          correctAnswer: "Machine language",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is not a characteristic of a computer?",
          options: ["Versatility", "Accuracy", "I.Q."],
          correctAnswer: "I.Q.",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is the smallest unit of data in a computer?",
          correctAnswer: "Bit",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is not a type of computer code?",
          options: ["EDIC", "ASCII", "BCD"],
          correctAnswer: "EDIC",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is designed to control the operations of a computer?",
          options: ["User", "Application Software", "System Software"],
          correctAnswer: "System Software",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: BIOS is used by the operating system.",
          correctAnswer: "True",
          type: "true or false"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      unitName: "Computer Architecture",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "Which device provides communication between a computer and the outer world?",
          options: ["Compact", "I/O", "Drivers"],
          correctAnswer: "I/O",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is not a type of computer on the basis of operation?",
          options: ["Digital", "Analog", "Remote"],
          correctAnswer: "Remote",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which type of computer is mostly used for automatic operations?",
          options: ["Analog", "Digital", "Hybrid"],
          correctAnswer: "Hybrid",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which invention gave birth to much cheaper microcomputers?",
          options: ["PDAs", "Microprocessors", "Microcomputers"],
          correctAnswer: "Microprocessors",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which type of computers are lower than mainframe computers in terms of speed and storage capacity?",
          options: ["Mainframes", "Hybrid", "Mini"],
          correctAnswer: "Mini",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "I/O function allows to exchange data directly between an ______ and the processor.",
          correctAnswer: "I/O module",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "Cache memory is intended to provide memory access _____",
          correctAnswer: "Fastest",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "A process is a _______.",
          options: ["Single thread of execution", "Program in the execution", "Program in the memory"],
          correctAnswer: "Program in the execution",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "How many color dots make up one color pixel on a screen?",
          correctAnswer: "3",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "Which natural element is the primary element in computer chips?",
          correctAnswer: "Silicon",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "History Of Computer": [
    {
      unitName: "Early Computers",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "Who is the father of Computers?",
          options: ["James Gosling", "Charles Babbage", "Dennis Ritchie"],
          correctAnswer: "Charles Babbage",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which is an example of first generation computer?",
          options: ["EDVAC", "EDSAC", "ENIAC"],
          correctAnswer: "ENIAC",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "When was Pascaline invented?",
          options: ["1617", "1620", "1642"],
          correctAnswer: "1642",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is the first computer to use Stored Program Concept?",
          options: ["UNIVAC", "ENIAC", "EDSAC"],
          correctAnswer: "EDSAC",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is the date when Babbage conceived Analytical engine?",
          options: ["1642", "1837", "1880"],
          correctAnswer: "1837",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "When was the vacuum tube invented?",
          options: ["1900", "1906", "1910"],
          correctAnswer: "1906",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "The first computer introduced in Nepal was",
          options: ["IBM 1400", "IBM 1401", "IBM 1402"],
          correctAnswer: "IBM 1401",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which was the most popular first generation computer?",
          options: ["IBM 1650", "IBM 360", "IBM 1130"],
          correctAnswer: "IBM 1650",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: The ENIAC was the first general-purpose electronic computer.",
          correctAnswer: "True",
          type: "true or false"
        },
        {
          question: "In which year was the UNIVAC I, the first commercial computer in the United States, delivered?",
          correctAnswer: "1951",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      unitName: "Computer Generations",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "How many major companies around the world manufacture microprocessors?",
          options: ["Only one company", "Two companies", "Three companies"],
          correctAnswer: "Two companies",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Operating system is used in which generation of computer for the first time?",
          options: ["First Generation", "Second Generation", "Third Generation"],
          correctAnswer: "Third Generation",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "From which generation were operating systems developed?",
          options: ["First", "Second", "Third"],
          correctAnswer: "Third",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Which generation of computers used transistors?",
          options: ["First", "Second", "Third"],
          correctAnswer: "Second",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "In which generation of computers were integrated circuits introduced?",
          correctAnswer: "Third",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: The fourth generation of computers introduced microprocessors.",
          correctAnswer: "True",
          type: "true or false"
        },
        {
          question: "Which generation of computers first used magnetic core memories?",
          options: ["First", "Second", "Third"],
          correctAnswer: "Second",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What technology was primarily used in first-generation computers?",
          correctAnswer: "Vacuum tubes",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "Which generation of computers introduced artificial intelligence?",
          options: ["Third", "Fourth", "Fifth"],
          correctAnswer: "Fifth",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: The speed of fourth-generation computers was measured in picoseconds.",
          correctAnswer: "False",
          type: "true or false"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "Data and Information": [
    {
      unitName: "Data Basics",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "This is the stage where data or instructions are put into a computer system.",
          options: ["Information", "Input", "Process"],
          correctAnswer: "Input",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Complete this equation: Data + ___ = Information",
          options: ["Meaning", "Data", "Numbers"],
          correctAnswer: "Meaning",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "These are raw facts, figures, values, or instructions with no specific meaning by themselves.",
          options: ["Information", "Data", "Meaning"],
          correctAnswer: "Data",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "This is processed information that comes out of a computer system.",
          options: ["Output", "Process", "Feedback"],
          correctAnswer: "Output",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "In a computer system, the stage between input and output is called __________________.",
          options: ["Processing", "Calculating", "Storage"],
          correctAnswer: "Processing",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "The term DATA came from the Latin root term:",
          options: ["Detem", "Datam", "Datum"],
          correctAnswer: "Datum",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "Two types of research data include:",
          options: ["Recognised and unrecognised data", "Structured and unstructured data", "Qualitative and quantitative data"],
          correctAnswer: "Qualitative and quantitative data",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is it called when the data is sourced from the place of origin?",
          options: ["Secondary", "Primary", "Tertiary"],
          correctAnswer: "Primary",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "What is it called when the data source is gathered and compiled with others?",
          options: ["Primary Data", "Gathered data", "Secondary data"],
          correctAnswer: "Secondary data",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: The collection of primary data is always more important than secondary data.",
          correctAnswer: "False",
          type: "true or false"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      unitName: "Information Processing",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "Data collected from an archive or the records of an organization is called:",
          options: ["Internal data", "Primary data", "External data"],
          correctAnswer: "Primary data",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "An individual trained in gathering data from the source is called:",
          options: ["Investigator", "Respondent", "Enumerator"],
          correctAnswer: "Enumerator",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: Primary data is also known as first-hand or original data.",
          correctAnswer: "True",
          type: "true or false"
        },
        {
          question: "______ can be defined as pictures, numbers, or words with no context.",
          options: ["Data", "Information", "Knowledge"],
          correctAnswer: "Data",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
        {
          question: "True or False: The data has to be converted into information for its usefulness.",
          correctAnswer: "True",
          type: "true or false"
        },
        {
          question: "The data that expresses or shows a certain amount is an example of ______ data.",
          correctAnswer: "quantitative",
          type: "fill in the blank"
        },
        {
          question: "____ is represented using graphs such as histograms, bar charts, scatter plots, etc.",
          options: ["Qualitative data", "Quantitative data", "Graphic data"],
          correctAnswer: "Quantitative data",
          type: "multiple choice"
        },
      ]
    },],
    // Add other categories
  };